Rehn Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, A-Z, 1858-1969, undated, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-15; 14.4 linear feet; Reels 5849-5869)
  - Lewis - Look, 1920-1966, undated (Box 8, Reel 5859, Frame 445-553)
    Lewis, Clarence
    Lewis Gallery
    Lewis, Harold
    Lewis, Hunt
    Lewis, Joan M.
    Lewis, John F.
    Lewis, Madison H.
    Lewisohn, Adolph
    Lewisohn, Sam A.
    Lewiston Evening Journal
    Libor, Henzion
    Library of Congress
    Liebman, Mrs. Charles J.
    Lieberman, Meyer F.
    Life
    Light, Robert M.
    Limited Editions Club
    Lincoln Safe Deposit Co.
    Lindborg, Carl
    Lindeberg, H. T.
    Lindquist, Gerald E.
    Line, Francis R.
    Lipscomb, Herbert C.
    Lissim, Linda
    Lister, Jeanne
    Little, Anna E.
    Little, Brown and Co.
    Little Gallery (Princeton)
    Little Gallery (Chatham, Mass.)
    Little Gallery in the Woods (See also Seachrist, Effie)
    Little Red School House
    Living American Art
    Livingston, Crawford
    Lloyd, Marion H.
    Locke, Caroline T.
    Lockman, DeWitt
    Lockwood, Helen D.
    Loeb, Judy Krueger
    Loew, Mellita S.
    Loew's Hotels
    Lofstrom, James E.
    Logan, Robert Fuller
    Long Beach Island Foundation of Art
    Longendyke, Adele
    Look
  - Lord - Luyber, 1925-1968, undated (Box 8, Reel 5859, Frame 554-675)
    Lord, Ann
    Lord, Don
    Lord, Evelyn Rumsey
    Lord, Rhoda
    Lorne, Naomi
    Los Angeles County Fair Association
    Los Angeles County Museum of History, Science and Art
    Louchheim, William S.
    Louisiana State University
    Louisvillve Art Association
    Lowe, Mrs. Arthur
    Joe and Emily Lowe Art Gallery (See University of Miami)
    Lowell Art Association
    Lowenthal, Milton and Edith
    Lowes, Raymond
    Lowman, Mrs. Lawrence
    Julius Lowy, Inc.
    Lubitz, Harvey
    Lucas, Charles C., Jr.
    Ludgin, Earle
    Ludington, Whight
    Luks, George and Maude C.
    Luks, Will
    J. Luria, Inc.
    Lutz, Dexter N.
    Luyber, Joseph
  - Lyall and Taylor Insurance - William Macbeth, Inc., 1919-1959, undated (Box 8, Reel 5859, Frame 676-774)
    Lyall and Taylor Insurance
    Lycett, Philip
    Lyde, J.
    Lyke, Hyatt
    Lyle, Henry H. M.
    Lyman Allyn Museum
    Lynde, J. U.
    Lyndon, A. J.
    Lyon, Winifred H.
    Lyster, Bernice
    MacArthur, Mr. and Mrs. Charles
    William Macbeth, Inc./Robert G. MacIntyre
  - MacDermott - R. H. Macy and Co., 1922-1968, undated (Box 8, Reel 5859, Frame 775-875)
    MacDermott, Stewart
    MacDonald, Joan
    MacDonald, John D.
    MacDonald, Rae
    MacDonald, Mrs. T. R.
    MacDowell Colony
    MacGregor Family
    MacIver, Ian T.
    Charles H. MacNider Museum
    R. H. Macy and Co.
  - Madden - Michael Malloy Gallery (Box 8, Reel 5859, Frame 876-956)
    Madden, Rena G.
    Madeira, Eleanor
    Thomas F. Madigan Autographs of Celebrities
    Magazine of Art
    Magee, Rena Tucker
    Magill, Arthur
    Magnolia Improvement Society
    Magriel, Paul
    Maguire, Mrs. R. S.
    Maine Art Gallery
    Maine Coast Artists
    Majer, Josef
    Maldarelli, O.
    Malinowski, Henry
    Malkin, Mrs. Henry
    Mallery, Rosemary
    Mallon, Paul
    Michael Malloy Gallery
  - Maloney - Mangione, 1927-1968, undated (Box 8, Reel 5859, Frame 957-1020)
    Maloney, Louise B.
    Manchester Trust Co.
    Mancuso, Frank
    Mandel, E. Estelle
    Mandelbaum, Robert A.
    Mandor, Milton
    Mangione, Pat and Jerry
  - Mangravite, Peppino, 1933-1968, (2 folders) (Box 8, Reel 5859, Frame 1021-1247)
  - Manhattan Eye, Ear, and Throat Hospital - Marquis, 1923-1967, undated (Box 8, Reel 5859, Frame 1248-1324)
    Manhattan Eye, Ear and Throat Hospital
    Manhattan Storage and Warehouse Co. (See also Morgan Brothers and the Manhattan Storage Co.)
    Mann, Alan N.
    Mansfield, Burton
    Mantz, Harold C.
    Manufacturers Life Insurance Co.
    Manufacturers Trust Co.
    Mapel, Betty Lou
    March, Mrs. Frederic
    Marcy, Bessie L.
    Marechal, Greet
    Marietta College
    Marin, Norma and John C., Jr.
    Mark, Jerome
    Markel, Betty
    Markowitz, Mrs. Irving
    Marquand, Mary
    Marquette University
    Marquis, Mrs. J. B.
  - Marsh - Mattatuck Museum, circa 1858-1967, undated (Box 8, Reel 5859, Frame 1325-1444)
    Marsh, James R.
    Marsh, Reginald and Felicia Meyer Marsh
    Marsh Estate
    Marshall, E. M.
    Marshall, Fey
    Marshall, Mrs. George
    Marshall, Lenore G.
    Mary Washington College
    Massilon Museum
    Master Institute of United Arts
    Matheson, D. A.
    Mathey, Dean
    Matt, D.
    Mattatuck Museum
  - Mattson, Henry and Daphne, 1925-1964 (Box 8, Reel 5859, Frame 1445-1566)
  - Mattson, Henry and Daphne, cont., 1925-1964 (Box 8, Reel 5860, Frame 13-56)
  - Matulka - McFadden, 1920-1962, undated (Box 8, Reel 5860, Frame 57-171)
    Matulka, Jan
    Mauran, William L.
    Mawhinney, Grace B.
    May, John E.
    May, Marjorie
    Mayer, Bena Frank
    Mayer, Francis G.
    Mayo, W. L.
    William Douglas McAdams, Inc.
    McBride, Henry
    McBride, Lucia M.
    McCabe, Jane Hall
    McCall Corp.
    McCann, Franklin T.
    McCann, Juliette
    McCarthy, Ed
    McCarthy, Richard D.
    McCarthy, William A.
    McClees Galleries
    McClintock, Pamela
    McCollum, Elaine
    McCoy, John W., II
    McCoy, Lawrence R.
    McCullough, Rea
    McCurrach, George A.
    McDermid, Alice C. and Ralph M.
    McDonough, Mrs. McEvoy, Jay
    McFadden, George
  - McFee, Henry Lee and Eleanor Fletcher, 1926-1968, (3 folders) (Box 8, Reel 5860, Frame 172-502)
  - Estate of Henry Lee and Eleanor Fletcher, 1953 (Box 8, Reel 5860, Frame 503-519)
  - McGibney - McVitty, 1918-1968, undated (Box 9, Reel 5860, Frame 521-627)
    McGibney, Bruce
    McGilvery, Laurence
    McGreevy, Milton
    McHugh, Alice P.
    McIlhenny, Henry P.
    McInnes, Mrs. Frank
    McIntyre, Anne H.
    McIntyre, Robert G. (See William MacBeth, Inc.)
    McKeand, W. M.
    McKillop, William
    McKim, William L.
    McLean, Doris Porter
    McLeod, G. L.
    McMillan, Mary
    McMurray, Elizabeth Ann
    Marion Koogler McNay Art Institute
    McRae, Frances E.
    McVeigh, Blake
    McVitty, Albert E.
  - Mearns - Merritt, 1920-1968, undated (Box 9, Reel 5860, Frame 628-724)
    Mearns, Hugh
    Mechau, Frank A. and Paula
    Mechenig, Ethel Love
    Medvin, Henry
    Meis, Mary
    Meilach, Donna Z.
    Melchers, Gary
    Meltzer, Paul
    Paul Meltzer Gallery (See also National Serigraph Society)
    Meltzer, Manford
    Meltzer, Milton
    Melville, Robert
    Memorial Art Gallery (See Rochester Memorial Art Gallery)
    Memphis Academy of Arts
    Mendelowitz, Daniel M.
    Mental Health Association of Westchester County, Inc.
    Merchandising Factors, Inc. Advertising
    Meredith, Burgess
    Meredith and Grew Real Estate
    Merida Gallery, Inc.
    Merrill, Charles E.
    Merritt, Arthur H.
  - Messick - Michigan State College, 1920-1967, undated (Box 9, Reel 5860, Frame 725-832)
    Messick, Ben
    Messmore, Carman
    Meta Mold Aluminum Co.
    Metcalf, Conger
    Metcalf, Elizabeth P.
    Metcalf, Houghton B.
    Metcalf, Thomas
    Metcalf, Willard L.
    Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Pictures (See Gibbons, Cedric)
    Metropolitan Galleries
    Metropolitan Museum of Art
    Metropolitan Young Artists Show
    Metz, M. R.
    Meyer, Felicia (See Marsh, Reginald and Felicia Meyer)
    Meyer, H. D.
    Meyer, Mrs. John D.
    Meyers, A.
    Meyers, Annette
    Meyers, Evelyn
    Miami Beach Public Library and Art Center
    Michigan State College/Michigan State University
  - Middendorf - Miller, 1920-1966, undated (Box 9, Reel 5860, Frame 833-925)
    Middendorf, J. William, II
    Middendorf, Robert
    Middlebury College
    Midtown Galleries
    E. and A. Milch, Inc./Milch Gallery
    Miller, Mrs. Byron D., Sr.
    Miller, Elam
    Miller, Flora Whitney
    Miller, Imogene P.
    Miller, John H.
    Miller, Kenneth Hayes and Helen
    Miller, Lawrence K.
    Miller, Max
    Miller, Robert Darrah
    Miller, Stanley H.
  - Milligan - Mint Museum of Art, 1927-1967, undated (Box 9, Reel 5860, Frame 926-1030)
    Milligan, Joan
    Millonzi, Robert I.
    Mills College
    Milwaukee Art Institute/Milwaukee Art Center
    Minewski, Alex
    Minneapolis Institute of Arts
    Minnesota State Fair
    Minster, Leonard B.
    Mint Museum of Art
  - Mintz - Moir, 1926-1968, undated (Box 9, Reel 5860, Frame 1031-1123)
    Mintz, Raymond
    Mississippi Art Association, Inc.
    Mitchell, Bruce
    Mitchell, Francis
    Mitchell, Phyllis H.
    Mitchell, William R. K.
    Mitcheson, Robert S. J.
    Mladinich, George (See also Athena Gallery, Inc.)
    Modern Art Studio
    Moessel, Julius
    Moffett, Ross
    Moir, Alexander
  - Montague - Monumental Storage and Carpet Cleaning Co., 1924-1966, undated (Box 9, Reel 5860, Frame 1124-1222)
    Montague, W. P.
    Montana State College
    Montclair Art Museum
    Montgomery, Anita C.
    Montreal, Mayor of
    Montreal Window Cleaning Co.
    Montross, N. E.
    Monumental Storage and Carpet Cleaning Co.
  - Moody's Inventors Service, Inc. - Mount Holyoke College, 1924-1967, undated (Box 9, Reel 5860, Frame 1223-1339)
    Moody's Investors Service, Inc.
    Moon, Owen, Jr.
    Moor Institute of Art, Science and Industry
    Moore, Fanny H.
    Moore Galleries
    Moore, Gladys G.
    Moore, Mrs. Joseph A., Jr.
    Moore, Martha E.
    Mopper, Coleman
    More, Herman
    Moreno, Jean Anderson
    Morey, Mrs. L. B.
    Morgan Brothers and the Manhattan Storage Co. (See also Manhattan Storage and Warehouse Co.)
    Morgan, John P., II
    Morgan, Patrick
    Morganthau, Mrs. Henry, Jr.
    Mories, B. L.
    Moross, Jerome
    Donald Morris Gallery
    Morris, Harrison S.
    Morris, Willamene S.
    Morrissey, Clara
    Morse, A. R.
    Morse, Margaret
    Morse, Peter
    Morse, Richard E.
    Morten, Marjory
    Morton, Mrs. David
    Morton, Richard H.
    Morton, Sylvia P. and Sterling
    Moses, Lillian L.
    Mott, Luther W.
    Mount, Charles Merrill
    Mount Holyoke College
  - Muir - Munson Williams Proctor Institute, 1924-1967, undated (Box 9, Reel 5860, Frame 1340-1466)
    Muir, Warner
    Mulcey, Paul A.
    Mulligan, Mrs. Ralph C.
    Mullins, Helene
    Munsell, Richard
    Munson, George S.
    Munson Williams Proctor Institute
  - Murdock - Murphy, 1918-1962, undated (Box 9, Reel 5860, Frame 1467-1572)
    Murdock, A. M.
    Murdock Louise P., Estate of
    Murphy, Catherine M.
    Murphy, Edward
    Murphy, Fred T.
    Murphy, Mrs. J. Francis
    Murphy, James P.
  - Museum of Art of Ogunquit, circa 1942-1968, undated (Box 9, Reel 5860, Frame 1573-1580)
  - Museum of Art of Ogunquit - Museum of contemporary Crafts, circa 1942-1968, undated (Box 9, Reel 5861, Frame 12-100)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston (See also School of the Museum of Fine Arts, Boston) - Museum of Fine Arts, Little Rock, 1934-1968, undated (Box 9, Reel 5861, Frame 101-161)
    Museum of Fine Arts, Boston
    Museum of Fine Arts, Houston
    Museum of Fine Arts, Little Rock
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1938-1968, (3 folders) (Box 9, Reel 5861, Frame 162-435)
  - Museum of New Mexico - National Academy of Design, 1921-1967, undated (Box 9, Reel 5861, Frame 436-531)
    Museum of New Mexico
    Museum of the City of New York
    Music Corporation of America
    Musselman, Darwin
    Musselman, David L.
    Mutual Benefit Life Insurance Co.
    Myers, Charles A., Jr.
    Myers, Jerome
    Mystic Art Association, Inc.
    Nadherny, Mrs.
    Nadler, D.
    Nagle, James W.
    Namuth, Hans
    Narell, Irena
    Nathan, Ann
    Nathan, Fred L.
    Nathanson, Bernard
    Nathanson, Win
    Nation
    National Academy of Design
  - National Aid to Visually Handicapped - National Gallery, 1940-1968, undated (Box 9, Reel 5861, Frame 532-652)
    National Aid to Visually Handicapped
    National Alliance of Art and Industry
    National Art Week
    National Association of Fine Arts Dealers, Inc.
    National Association of Women Artists
    National City Bank
    National Collection of Fine Arts (See Smithsonian Institution)
    National Conference of Christians and Jews
    National Council of Jewish Women, Essex County Section
    National Council of Jewish Women, Patterson Section
    National Council of Jewish Women, Westport Section
    National Council of Women of the United States, Inc.
    National Cystic Fibrosis Research Foundation
    National Gallery
  - National Institute of Arts and Letters - Rolf Nelson Gallery, 1919-1964, undated (Box 9, Reel 5861, Frame 653-703)
    National Institute of Arts and Letters
    National Jewish Hospital at Denver
    National Serigraph Society/Serigraph Galleries (See also Meltzer Gallery)
    National Society of Mural Painters
    National Town and Country Club, New York Chapter
    Nauman, F. R.
    Navas, Elizabeth (See Murdock, Louise P., Estate of)
    Neague, Anna
    Neale, Mrs. Charles T.
    Nebel, Rose
    Nebraska Art Association
    Neikrug, Mrs. S.
    Neiman-Marcus
    Nelson, Mr. and Mrs. George Laurence
    Nelson, Prudence
    Rolf Nelson Gallery
  - William Rockhill Nelson Gallery/William Rockhill Nelson Gallery and Atkins Museum of Fine Arts, 1940-1962 (Box 9, Reel 5861, Frame 704-778)
  - Nesin - New York Leader, 1926-1968, undated (Box 9, Reel 5861, Frame 779-858)
    Nesin, Rose A.
    Netherlands Information Service
    Netherlands Insurance Co.
    Netter, Terrence
    Neuberger, Roy R.
    Neville, Mrs. John F.
    New Amsterdam Casualty Co.
    New Canaan Library Art Committee
    New England Telephone and Telegraph Co.
    New Gallery, Inc.
    New Jersey State Museum
    New School
    New World Illustrated
    New York Arts Festival
    New York Association for the Blind
    New York Central Lines
    New York City, Board of Education
    New York City, Bureau of Records
    New York City, Department of Finance
    New York City, Department of Health
    New York City, Department of Welfare
    New York County Supreme Court
    New York Edison Co.
    New York Guild for the Jewish Blind
    New York Historical Society
    New York Infirmary
    New York Journal American
    New York Leader
  - New York Psychoanalytic Institute - New York Woman, 1919-1968, undated (Box 9, Reel 5861, Frame 859-956)
    New York Psychoanalytic Institute
    New York Public Library
    New York Regional Art Council
    New York Society for Ethical Culture/Fieldston-Ethical Alumni Association
    New York State, Department of Law
    New York State, Department of Taxation and Finance
    New York State, Division of Employment
    New York State, Income Tax Bureau
    New York State Education
    New York State Exposition
    New York Telephone Co.
    New York Times
    New York Trust Co.
    New York University
    New York Woman
  - New Yorker - Nittany Lion Inn, 1918-1968, undated (Box 9, Reel 5861, Frame 957-1094)
    New Yorker
    Newark Museum Association/Newark Museum
    Newberry, John S., Jr.
    Newbold, T. T.
    Newcomb, Macklin and Co.
    Newdorf, Mr.
    Newell-Emmett Company
    M. A. Newhouse and Son
    Newkirk, Kenneth
    Newman, Robert L.
    Newman, Roslyn
    Newsweek
    Newton, Mr. and Mrs. J. R.
    Newton, Max
    Newton, Parker
    Nichols, Mrs. Charles W.
    Nichols, Spencer
    Nicolosi, Lucy
    Nieman, Harry
    Niese, Henry
    Niesley, Elise
    Nikkel, Vernon
    Nisbet, Robert H.
    Nisenson, Alvin
    Nishida, H.
    Nittany Lion Inn
  - Noehren - Oalses, 1918-1968, undated (Box 10, Reel 5861, Frame 1096-1188)
    Noehren, Theodore
    Nordness Gallery
    Norfolk Museum of Arts and Sciences
    North Carolina State College of Agriculture
    North Shore Arts Festival
    North Shore Breeze
    North Shore Child Guidance Association
    North Shore Press, Inc.
    Norton Gallery and School of Art/Palm Beach Art League, Inc.
    Norton, Gertrude M.
    Norton, Louis D.
    Norton, Ralph H. (See Norton Gallery and School of Art/Palm Beach Art League, Inc.)
    Norton, Mrs. Thomas H.
    Noselson, Kalman Uris
    Notman and Co.
    November, Sara D.
    Oakland Art Museum
    Oalses, Mrs. John B.
  - Oberlin College - Ogilvie, 1919-1968, undated (Box 10, Reel 5861, Frame 1189-1304)
    Oberlin College
    Oberteuffer, George and May P. F.
    M. O'Brien and Son
    O'Brien's Art Emporium
    Oceanside and Cottages
    Ochtman, Dorothy
    O'Connell, J. Harlin
    O'Connor, John, Jr.
    O'Connor, Joseph J.
    Odom, Jamie
    O'Dowd, John A.
    Oehlschlaeger, Frank J.
    Oenslaeger, Donald
    Office of Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs
    Offin Advertising/Charles Z. Offin
    Ogilvie, Hanson S.
  - O'Hara - Owen Gallery, Inc., 1918-1968, undated (Box 10, Reel 5861, Frame 1305-1410)
    O'Hara, Shirley Putnam (Mrs. Eliot)
    Ohio State University
    Ohio Water Color Society
    Oklahoma Art Center
    Oklahoma Print Makers Society
    Old Mill Gallery
    Old Print Shop, Inc.
    Old Town Galleries
    Olds, Elizabeth
    Olds, George S.
    Olds, Halsey Knapt
    Olds, Stoughton
    O'Leary, Edward
    Olinger, Grover
    O'Neil, Cyril F., Jr.
    O'Neill, C. F.
    Oppenhiem, Laurent
    O'Reilly, Edward G.
    O'Reilly, Thomas J.
    Orling, Anne
    Ornstein, Peter
    O'Rourke, Gladys
    Orr, Elliott
    Orviz, Mrs. Hardin
    Osborne, Robert G.
    Ossorio, Josephine B.
    Osterkamp-Mead Corp.
    Overlook
    Overseas Press Club of America, Inc.
    Owen Gallery, Inc.
  - Owen Gallery, Inc., cont., 1918-1968, undated (Box 10, Reel 5862, Frame 13)
  - Pacific Art Review - Park Gallery, 1920-1967, undated (Box 10, Reel 5862, Frame 15-107)
    Pacific Art Review
    Packard, Edwin
    Packard, Rosa Covington
    Padawer Prize for Drawing
    Paddock, Willard
    Page, Ruth
    Pagent
    Paine, P. S.
    Paintings of the Year (See Pepsi Cola's Annual Art Competition)
    Pall, David B. and Helen R.
    Palm Beach Art League, Inc. (See Norton Gallery and School of Art)
    Palm Beach Galleries
    Palmedo, Roland
    Palmer, Edla W.
    Palmer, Fred L.
    Palmer, George S.
    Palmer, Mrs. Paul
    Palmer, William H.
    Palmer, William J.
    Pancoast, Minnie
    Paradise, Phil
    Paramount Die Casting Co.
    Park East News, Inc.
    Park Avenue Gallery
    Park Gallery
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries, Inc. - Pease and Elliman, 1919-1966, undated (Box 10, Reel 5862, Frame 108-213)
    Parke-Bernet Galleries, Inc.
    Parker, Evelyn Naegle
    Parker, George
    Parker, Inez Grant
    King Parker, Inc.
    Parker, Mrs.
    Parkin, Jewell
    Parkinson, Elizabeth
    Parks, Henry Francis
    Parris Art Museum
    Parsons, Virginia B.
    Paskus, Gordon and Hyman
    Passedoit Gallery
    Patrick, James H.
    Pattison, Priscilla
    Paul, D.
    Paullin, Ethel Parsons
    Paxton, John L.
    Payson, Joan
    Peabody, Julian
    Pearce, Josephine S.
    Pearce, W. Ray
    Pearlman, Samuel
    Pease, Mrs. F. R.
    Pease and Elliman
  - Pedlar and Ryan, Inc. - Penney, 1924-1967, undated (Box 10, Reel 5862, Frame 214-291)
    Pedlar and Ryan, Inc.
    Pell, Madeline B.
    Penguin Books, Inc.
    Penguin Studio
    Penn, Dorothy N.
    William Penn Publishing Corporation
    Penney, Charles P., Jr.
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 1919-1966, (3 folders) (Box 10, Reel 5862, Frame 292-500)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - Phelps, 1919-1968, undated (Box 10, Reel 5862, Frame 501-631)
    Pennsylvania Railroad
    Pennsylvania State College/Pennsylvania State University
    Pensacola, Florida, Chamber of Commerce
    Pepper, Charles Hovey
    Pepsi Cola's Annual Art Competition, Paintings of the Year
    Perkins, Harley
    Frank Perls Gallery
    Perrine, Van Deering
    Perry, Louis
    Persons, Simmons
    Perutz, George J.
    Peter, Armistead, III
    Peters, Philip H., Jr.
    Pettersen, Richard
    Pettus, Isabelle M.
    Pfeiffer, Charles Leonard
    Pfeiffer, Heinrich
    Phelps, George A.
  - Philadelphia Art Alliance, 1924-1964 (Box 10, Reel 5862, Frame 632-717)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art - Philbrook Art Center, 1944-1967, undated (Box 10, Reel 5862, Frame 718-843)
    Philadelphia Museum of Art
    Philadelphia Trade and Convention Center
    Philadelphia Water Color Society
    Philbrook Art Center
  - Philips, Duncan/Phillips Memorial Gallery/Phillips Gallery/Phillips Collection, 1919-1964, (2 folders) (Box 10, Reel 5862, Frame 844-1031)
  - Phillips Exeter Academy - Piedmont Festival, Inc., 1927-1967, undated (Box 10, Reel 5862, Frame 1032-1152)
    Phillips Exeter Academy, Lamont Gallery
    Phillips, N. C.
    Phillips, W. E.
    Phipps, Mrs. John S.
    Phipps, Mr. and Mrs. Ogden
    Phoenix Art Museum
    Phoenix Engraving Co.
    Phoenix Fine Arts Association
    Picarello, Frank E.
    Picken, George
    Pickett, Grace
    Blanche and Jerome W. Pickett Foundation
    Pictures on Exhibit
    Piedmont Festival, Inc.
  - Pigmalion - Poor, Ann, 1924-1965, undated (Box 10, Reel 5862, Frame 1153-1222)
    Pigmalion
    Pillsbury, Jane
    Pioneer Museum and Haggin Galleries
    Piper, Raymond F.
    Pirie, Robert
    Pitcairn, Raymond
    Pitman and Brown Co.
    Pitt Scott Corp.
    Pittsburgh Building Co.
    Pittsburgh Post
    Pittsburgh Water Color Society
    Pizzini, Irene S.
    Platt, Mrs. Geoffrey
    Plavcan, Joseph M.
    Plaza Art Galleries, Inc.
    Pleadwell, Theodora
    Plumb, Ralph
    Plunguian, Gina
    Pocket Books, Inc.
    Police Athletic League, Inc.
    R. L. Polk and Co., Inc.
    Pollack, Augustus
    Pollet, Joseph
    Pollock, Muriel
    Pomeroy, Elsie Tower
    Pomeroy, Henry K.
    Pomfret School
    Pougialis, Constantine
    Poon, Daniel
    Poor, Ann
  - Poor, Henry Varnum, 1940-1967, (2 folders) (Box 10, Reel 5862, Frame 1223-1407)
  - Poor Richard Club of Philadelphia - Popolizio, Vincent J., circa 1919-1966, undated (Box 10, Reel 5862, Frame 1408-1432)
    Poor Richard Club of Philadelphia
    Poplack, Richard M.
    Poplack, William J.
    Popolizio, Vincent J.
  - Port-A-Wall - Potter, circa 1919-1966, undated (Box 10, Reel 5863, Frame 12-70)
    Port-A-Wall
    Porter, C. B.
    Porter, Fairfield
    Porter, James W.
    Portland Art Museum (Oregon)
    Portland Museum of Art (Maine)
    Portraits, Inc.
    Posner, John Jacob
    Post, Georgia A.
    Post
    Post, Shelley
    Postgraduate Center for Psychotherapy, Inc.
    Postmaster, Grand Central Station
    Potamkin, Mrs. M. P.
    Potomac School
    Potter, Mrs. H. A.
    Potter, Mrs. John B.
    Potter, Mrs. William J.
  - Powell - Provincetown Arts Festival, 1924-1966, undated (Box 10, Reel 5863, Frame 71-177)
    Powell, Adelaide
    Powell, Leslie
    Powell, Mrs. T. I. Hare
    Powers, Richard Gorman
    Powers, Richard M.
    Pratt, George W.
    Preiss Trading Corp.
    Prendergast, Charles W.
    Prentice, Mr. and Mrs. Clarence C.
    Prentice-Hall, Inc.
    Presnal, W. B.
    Pressler, Frederick
    Preston, Malcolm H.
    Prezzi, Wilma
    Price, E. Y.
    Vincent Price Collection (See Sears, Roebuck and Co.)
    Princeton Merchants' Exhibition
    Print Club
    Proctor, Eleanor M.
    Profile Press
    Promenade
    Providence Art Club
    Provincetown Art Association
    Provincetown Arts Festival
  - Psaropulos - Raffo, 1921-1967, undated (Box 10, Reel 5863, Frame 178-266)
    Psaropulos, Theodore
    Public Education Association
    Publicover, W. A.
    Pueblo Junior College
    Pulitzer, Ralph
    Pulling, Edward
    Purdue University
    Purvis, Don
    Puterbaugh, Edith L.
    Putnam, Esther W.
    Pyle, Mrs. Howard
    Quaker Ridge Parent Teacher Association
    Quarrie Corp. Publishers
    Quinby, Henry C.
    Quinlan, Laura
    Quirk, Francis J.
    Rabin, Nathan
    Ernest Raboff Gallery
    Alexander Rabow Galleries
    Radwick, R. Vance
    Raffo, Steve
  - Rahming - Randolph, 1940-1968, undated (Box 11, Reel 5863, Frame 268-332)
    Rahming, Mrs. Norris
    Rahr, Mrs. Philip